<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<PizzaList>
	<Flavor id="1">
		<Flabor>Cheese Pizza</Flabor>
		<Discription>
			It should be no shocker that a classic is the statistical favorite.
			Cheese pizza is one of the most popular choices.
			It will always be a simple,
			unadorned masterpiece on its own.
		</Discription>
		<Price>
			<Size>
				<a>Large  8 Slice  - 200</a>
				<b>Medium 6 Slice  - 150</b>
				<c>Small  4 Slice  - 100</c>
			</Size>
		</Price>
		<AddsOn>
		<tappings>
			Ground pork - 20
			Bellpepper  - 20
		</tappings>
		</AddsOn>
		<INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
			<Ingredient>
				GROUND PORK
				ITALIAN SEASONING
				TOMATO SAUCE
				MADE PIZZA DOUGH
				SHREDDED
				ONION, CHOPPED
				RED BELL PEPPER, SLICED
				OLIVES, SLICED
			</Ingredient>
			<Nutrition>
				<Benifits>
					Calories 213.
					Total Fat 7.8g 10%
					Saturated Fat 3.6g 18%
					Trans Fat 0.2g.
					Polyunsaturated Fat 1.4g.
					Monounsaturated Fat 2.1g.
					Cholesterol 14mg 5%
					Sodium 478mg 21%
				</Benifits>
			</Nutrition>
		</INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
		<TimeToCook>
			<minutes>10-15</minutes>
			<Second>0</Second>
		</TimeToCook>
		<HeatDegrees>
			<Degrees>400F</Degrees>
		</HeatDegrees>
		<COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
			<a>Step 1 In a pan, saute with Italian seasoning. Set aside.
			Step 2 Spread the tomato sauce evenly on the pizza dough and top with shredded cheese,, onion, bell pepper, and olives.
			Step 3 To cook the cheesy pizza, preheat the oven to 400F and bake for 10-15 minutes or until the cheese has melted and the sides of the pizza are crisp and golden brown.</a>
		</COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
		<Top10PizzaStore>
			<StoreName>1Trattoria Altrove
			2) Amare La Cucina
			3) Da Gianni Cucina Italiana
			4) Yellow Cab
			5) Cibo
			6) Salvatore Cuomo/Bar
			7) Stephen’s Brick Oven Pizza
			8) Wildflour
			9) Francesco’s Kitchen
			10) Mamma Mia</StoreName>
		</Top10PizzaStore>
	</Flavor>
	
	
	
	<Flavor id="2">
		<Flabor>Veggie Pizza</Flabor>
		<Discription>
			When you want to jazz up your cheese pizza with color and texture,
			veggies are the perfect topping. And you’re only limited by your imagination.
			Everything from peppers and mushrooms,
			to eggplant and onions make for an exciting and tasty veggie pizza.
		</Discription>
		<Price>
			<Size>
				Large  8 Slice  - 300
				Medium 6 Slice  - 250
				Small  4 Slice  - 200
			</Size>		
		</Price>
		<AddsOn>
			<tappings>
				Ground pork - 20
				Bellpepper  - 20
				Eggplant	- 20
				mushrooms	- 20
			</tappings>
		</AddsOn>
		<INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
			<Ingredient>
				Pizza Sauce
				Baby Spinach
				Part-Skim Mozzarella
				Artichoke
				Bell Pepper
				Red Onion
				Cherry Tomatoes
				Olives
				Sliced Almonds
				Optional Garnishes
			</Ingredient>
			<Nutrition>
				<Benifits>
					Calories 370.
					Total Fat 14g 18%
					Saturated Fat 6.1g 31%
					Trans Fat 0.3g.
					Polyunsaturated Fat 2.3g.
					Monounsaturated Fat 4.2g.
					Cholesterol 23mg 8%
					Sodium 867mg 38%
				</Benifits>	
			</Nutrition>
		</INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
		<TimeToCook>
			<minutes>10-12</minutes>
			<Second>0</Second>
		</TimeToCook>
		<HeatDegrees>
			<Degrees>400F</Degrees>
		</HeatDegrees>
		<COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
			<a>To cook the pizza, preheat your oven to 400 degrees fahrenheit.
			Remove all the packing, place the pizza directly on the middle oven rack for 15 to 18 minutes.
			Once the crust is golden brown and the cheese is nice and melted,
			let the pizza stand for about two minutes before slicing.</a>
		</COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
		<Top10PizzaStore>
			<StoreName>
				1) Trattoria Altrove
				2) Amare La Cucina
				3) Da Gianni Cucina Italiana
				4) Yellow Cab
				5) Cibo
				6) Salvatore Cuomo/Bar
				7) Stephen’s Brick Oven Pizza
				8) Wildflour
				9) Francesco’s Kitchen
				10) Mamma Mia
			</StoreName>
		</Top10PizzaStore>
	</Flavor>
	
	
	
	<Flavor id="3">
		<Flabor>Pepperoni Pizza</Flabor>
		<Discription>
			There’s a reason this is one of the most popular types of pizza.
			Who doesn’t love biting into a crispy, salty round of pepperoni.
		</Discription>
		<Price>
			<Size>
				<a>Large  8 Slice  - 200</a>
				<b>Medium 6 Slice  - 150</b>
				<c>Small  4 Slice  - 100</c>
			</Size>
		</Price>
		<AddsOn>
			<tappings>
				Pepperoni - 20
			</tappings>
		</AddsOns>
		<INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
			<Ingredient>
				pizza sauce
				pepperoni
				mozzarella cheese, grated
				black pepper
			</Ingredient>
			<Nutrition>
				<Benifits>
					Calories 440.
					Total Fat 21 g.
					Cholesterol 50 mg.
					Sodium 820 mg.
					Carbohydrates 34 g.
					Protein 23 g.
					Ingredients:
				</Benifits>
			</Nutrition>
		</INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
		<TimeToCook>
			<minutes>12-15</minutes>
			<Second>0</Second>
		</TimeToCook>
		<HeatDegrees>
			<Degrees>400F</Degrees>
		</HeatDegrees>
		<COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
			<a>TPreheat your oven to 400 degrees Fahrenheit,
			then toss the pizza inside for about 20 minutes
			(ours took a bit longer than that; we left it in for about 25 minutes).
			The instructions say to place the pizza directly on the center rack,
			but we used a baking sheet, like we always do</a>
		</COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
		<Top10PizzaStore>
			<StoreName>
				1) Trattoria Altrove
				2) Amare La Cucina
				3) Da Gianni Cucina Italiana
				4) Yellow Cab
				5) Cibo
				6) Salvatore Cuomo/Bar
				7) Stephen’s Brick Oven Pizza
				8) Wildflour
				9) Francesco’s Kitchen
				10) Mamma Mia
			</StoreName>
		</Top10PizzaStore>
	</Flavor>
	
	
	<Flavor id="4">
		<Flabor>Hawaiian Pizza</Flabor>
		<Discription>
			TPineapple might not be the first thing that comes to mind when you think pizza.
			But add in some ham and it creates an unexpectedly solid
			sweet and salty combination for this type of pizza.
		</Discription>
		<Price>
			<Size>
				<a>Large  8 Slice  - 250</a>
				<b>Medium 6 Slice  - 170</b>
				<c>Small  4 Slice  - 120</c>
			</Size>
		</Price>
		<AddsOn>
			<tappings>
				pineapple chunks - 20
				bacon			 - 20
			</tappings>
		</AddsOn>
		<INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
			<Ingredient>
				olive oil,
				cornmeal
				pizza sauce
				mozzarella cheese
				ham or Canadian bacon, sliced or chopped
				pineapple chunks
				bacon, cooked and crumbled
			</Ingredient>

			<Nutrition>
				<Benifits>
					carbs 37g.
					Fiber2g.
					Total Carbs.39g.
					Protein.12g.
					Fats 6g.
				</Benifits>
			</Nutrition>
		</INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
		<TimeToCook>
			<minutes>15-20</minutes>
			<Second>0</Second>
		</TimeToCook>
		<HeatDegrees>
			<Degrees>475F</Degrees>
		</HeatDegrees>
		<COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
			<a>Preheat oven to 475°F (246°C).
			Allow it to heat for at least 15–20 minutes as you
			shape the pizza in the next step. If using a pizza
			stone, place it in the oven to preheat as well.
			Lightly grease a large baking sheet or pizza pan with 1/2
			Tablespoon of olive oil. Sprinkle lightly with cornmeal,
			which gives the crust extra crunch and flavor.
			Shape the dough: When the homemade dough is ready,
			punch it down to release any air bubbles. Divide
			the dough in half and freeze half the dough for another
			time—see freezing instructions in the pizza dough recipe.
			On a lightly floured work surface using lightly floured hands or
			rolling pin, gently flatten the dough into a disc. Place on prepared pan and,
			using lightly floured hands, stretch and flatten the disc into a 12-inch circle,
			about 1/2-inch thick. If the dough keeps shrinking back as you try to stretch it,
			stop what you’re doing, cover it lightly and let it rest for 5–10 minutes, then try again.
			Once shaped into a 12-inch circle, lift the edge of the dough up to create a lip around the edges.
			I simply pinch the edges up to create the rim. If using a pizza stone,
			place the dough directly on a baker’s peel dusted with cornmeal.
			Cover dough lightly with plastic wrap or a clean kitchen towel and allow to rest for a few minutes as you
			gather the pizza toppings.</a>
		</COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
		<Top10PizzaStore>
			<StoreName>
				1) Trattoria Altrove
				2) Amare La Cucina
				3) Da Gianni Cucina Italiana
				4) Yellow Cab
				5) Cibo
				6) Salvatore Cuomo/Bar
				7) Stephen’s Brick Oven Pizza
				8) Wildflour
				9) Francesco’s Kitchen
				10) Mamma Mia
			</StoreName>
		</Top10PizzaStore>
	</Flavor>
	
	
	
	<Flavor id="5">
		<Flabor>The Works Pizza</Flabor>
		<Discription>
			<a>And when the supreme just isn’t enough,
			you’re ready for the works. It’s a step up in heartiness from the supreme.
			The “works” usually involves a wide variety of veggie toppings including onions,
			olives, and mushrooms, plus bacon and pepperoni.</a>
		</Discription>
		<Price>
			<Size>
				<a>Large  8 Slice  - 250</a>
				<b>Medium 6 Slice  - 170</b>
				<c>Small  4 Slice  - 120</c>
			</Size>
		</Price>
		<AddsOn>
			<tappings>
				pepperoni - 20
				julienne-cut Canadian bacon - 20
				spicy Italian sausage - 50
				mozzarella cheese - 20
				fresh-cut onions - 20
				crisp green peppers - 20
				ripe black olives -20
				mushrooms
			</tappings>
		</AddsOn>
		<INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
			<Ingredient>
				pepperoni
				julienne-cut Canadian bacon
				spicy Italian sausage
				mozzarella cheese
				fresh-cut onions
				crisp green peppers
				ripe black olives
				mushrooms
			</Ingredient>

			<Nutrition>
				alories.368.4 kCal.
				Total Carbs.41 g. Net Carbs.
				37.1 g. Fiber. 3.8 g.
				Starch. - Sugar. 7.4 g.
				Sugar Alcohols.
				-Protein. 15.8 g.
				Fat. 15.7 g.
				Monounsat. Fat. 5.6 g.
				Polyunsat. Fat. 2.9 g.
				Saturated Fat. 5.8 g.
				Cholesterol. 32.2 mg.
				Glycemic Load. -
			</Nutrition>
		</INGREDIENTS-Nutrition>
		<TimeToCook>
			<minutes>20-25</minutes>
			<Second>00</Second>
		</TimeToCook>
		<HeatDegrees>
			<Degrees>450F</Degrees>
		</HeatDegrees>
		<COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
			<a>
				Step 1 Preheat oven to 450°.
				
				Step 2 To prepare topping,
				heat 1 teaspoon olive oil in a heavy medium skillet over medium heat.
				Cook sausage in hot oil 5 minutes or until browned; stir to crumble.
				Add bell pepper, mushrooms, and onion; cook 4 minutes or until vegetables
				are tender, stirring occasionally. Add garlic; sauté 1 minute. Stir in olives;
				drain sausage mixture on paper towels.

				Step 3 To prepare crust, dissolve yeast and 1/2 teaspoon sugar
				in warm soy milk in a small bowl; let stand 5 minutes.

				Step 4 Weigh or lightly spoon 3 ounces brown rice flour (3/4 cup) into dry measuring cups;
				level with a knife. Place brown rice flour, remaining 2 teaspoons sugar, cornstarch,
				and next 3 ingredients in a food processor.
				With processor on, pour yeast mixture, 1 tablespoon olive oil,
				and vinegar through food chute; process 30 seconds, adding 2
				tablespoons brown rice flour, 1 tablespoon at a time if necessary,
				until mixture forms a ball.

				Step 5Coat a 12-inch pizza pan with cooking spray. Place dough on pan;
				dust with remaining 2 tablespoons brown rice flour to prevent sticking to fingers.
				Press dough onto pan; crimp edges of dough with fingers to form a rim.
				Place on bottom rack of oven.

				Step 6 Bake at 450° for 10 minutes.
				Remove from oven, and brush edges of crust with remaining 1 teaspoon olive oil.
				Spread pizza sauce evenly over crust. Top with sausage mixture and cheese.
				Place on middle rack of oven. Bake at 450° for 15 minutes.
				Cool pizza in pan on a wire rack 5 minutes. Cut into 6 wedges.

				Step 7Cooking Tip Xanthan gum is a corn-based product often used in gluten-free baking as a
				substitute for wheat gluten to thicken and bind. Using too much can result in a baked good
				that is heavy or gummy, so be sure to measure carefully. Most recipes call for 1 to 2
				teaspoons—a little can go a long way.
			</a>
		</COOKINGINSTRUCTIONS>
		<Top10PizzaStore>
			<StoreName>
				1) Trattoria Altrove
				2) Amare La Cucina
				3) Da Gianni Cucina Italiana
				4) Yellow Cab
				5) Cibo
				6) Salvatore Cuomo/Bar
				7) Stephen’s Brick Oven Pizza
				8) Wildflour
				9) Francesco’s Kitchen
				10) Mamma Mia
			</StoreName>
		</Top10PizzaStore>
	</Flavor>
</PizzaList>
